Love on a Limb is a tv movie, romance film directed by Mel Damski.
Aimie Roarke is always up for a cause and when the town’s beloved Oak tree is
set to be cut down, she takes it upon herself try and save it.
When the Mayor hires a handsome new landscaper to cut it down, she decides
the only way to save the tree is to chain herself to it.
As Kyle attempts to wait her out and the two start to spend more time together, they may find the
Old Tree brings them both more than they could have imagined in life and love.
Aimie Roarke, played by Ashley Williams.
Kyle Sorenson, played by Trevor Donovan.
Zee Roarke, played by Marilu Henner.
Sheriff Larry Garibaldi, played by Ron Lea.
Loan Officer, played by Xavier Sotelo.
Mayor Tom Parker, played by Jefferson Brown.
Out on a Limb is an autobiographical book written by American
film actress and dancer Shirley MacLaine in 1983.
It details MacLaine's journeys through New Age spirituality.
The book follows her from southern California to various locations including New York City,
Europe, and Hawaii, culminating in a life-changing trip to the Andes Mountains in Peru.
Central characters include David who is, according to MacLaine, a composite character; Gerry Stamford, a married man and fictionalized Labour member of
the British House of Commons, with whom MacLaine claimed she had a love affair; and real-life close friend and politician, Bella Abzug.
The book received both acclaim and criticism for its candor in dealing with such topics as
reincarnation, meditation, mediumship (trance-channeling), and even unidentified flying objects.
It made Shirley MacLaine the butt of many jokes,
especially by late-night television comedians.
Once, when David Letterman would not let up on the New Age subject, she responded by saying, "Maybe Cher was right; maybe you are
an asshole!" The claim about an affair with the MP gained attention in the UK when the book was published there.
Out on a Limb was adapted for television broadcast in 1987.
The five-hour ABC miniseries starred MacLaine (as herself), John Heard
as David Manning, and Charles Dance as Gerry Stamford.
Anne Jackson played Bella Abzug, and Jerry Orbach played Shirley's agent.
MacLaine kept a diary during the filming of the miniseries.
The notes were later turned into the book It's All In the Playing.
After the publication the former President Jimmy
Carter asked MacLaine to talk about UFOs.
...Looking back, I can say that making that simple, lazy afternoon decision to visit an unusual bookstore [the
Bodhi Tree Bookstore in West Hollywood] was one of the most important decisions of my life.
The tone is emotional.